III - Athletics
看着你留下的笔记 我才知道你想要的答案
I read your note and I know just what you want to hear
时间会治愈疼痛 但我不会因此而变得坚强
It hurts less over time but I'm not getting stronger
我只是把一部分疼痛抛诸脑后
I just leave pieces behind
在我粉身碎骨 面目全非之前 我只能多次下坠
And I can only fall so many times before I'm broke unrecognizable
现在我能给予的只剩下这些零星的碎片
Now all I've left to give is the piece that still remains
你把这些零星碎片带走
And you bring the pieces back
爱情只给我带来痛苦
Love it only reconstructs the pain
时光凝固静止 我才惊觉你曾是我的一切
As time fails to elapse I'm finding you were everything to me
如今我的前尘后世都会以悲剧收场
Now my future and my past are ending tragically the same